<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on zzz</title>
    <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on zzz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 14:50:31 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;Binance: Buy Bitcoin &amp; Crypto&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/binance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 14:50:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/binance/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Binance is a world-leading cryptocurrency trading platform that provides low-fee trading services and supports more than 200 cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Chainlink, and Cardano. Users can easily buy and sell cryptocurrencies and enjoy 24/7 customer support and currency price alerts. In addition, Binance also provides high-yield cryptocurrency deposit and staking services, where users can earn interest and even spend at more than 50 million merchants around the world through the Binance card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;HomeServe - Home Repair&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/homeserve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:04:29 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/homeserve/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction If you have a HomeServe plan, you can easily manage your HomeServe account from your mobile device. Simply log in to My Account with your HomeServe ID and you&amp;rsquo;ll have quick access to: View your existing HomeServe plans, Make payments, Update payment options, Go paperless, Reset HomeServe ID password, Add/cancel coverage, Schedule service, View service history and Chat with a HomeServe representative.&#xA;Affected version 3.3.4&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;Life : Personal Diary, Journal&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/life-personal-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:02:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/life-personal-diary/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction A personal and secure diary app. Write your life journey and keep those memories forever. You can also write journals, notes, to do lists and your daily plans in this diary app. It is also a note keeper, you can keep your notes in this diary app. It is a pocket diary where you can express yourself. Write your secrets and feeling in this life diary. Keep your life memorable life moments and milestones in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;Schlage Home&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/schlage-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:20:17 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/schlage-home/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction The Schlage Home app lets you conveniently control and monitor your locks from your smartphone over a secure, encrypted connection and pair your locks with leading smart home devices. This app works with the Schlage Encode Plus™ Smart WiFi Deadbolt, Schlage Encode™ Smart WiFi Deadbolt, Schlage Encode™ Smart WiFi Lever and Schlage Sense® Smart Deadbolt! with Schlage Sense® Smart Deadbolt. The Schlage Home app for Apple Watch works with Schlage Encode™ Smart WiFi Deadbolt and Smart WiFi Lever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;ReserveAmerica Camping&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/reserveamerica-camping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:19:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/reserveamerica-camping/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Use ReserveAmerica app to search on a map of states, federally available campgrounds and RV sites, yurts, cabins galore, private parks, and car camping in the U.S. Search by location, date, or amenity and display search results. View campground details, reviews and photos. Even saving your search settings makes finding your next campground as easy as opening the app.&#xA;Affected version 4.17.2.0&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;SMS text messaging app&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/sms-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:26:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/sms-text/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Simple and fast SMS application that you can use to send SMS to your friends, family and people you know.Features:Night mode option, Color customization option, Block unwanted spam SMS, Organize all your messages in folders, Support for emoticons, Appointment for sending messages, Group messages, Delayed sending, Support dual SIM cards, Message search option, Customize fonts, Change text size, Fixed messages, Backup and restore all your messages.&#xA;Affected version 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;Nicegram&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/nicegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:25:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/nicegram/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Nicegram is an alternative Telegram client, equipped with a set of innovative AI-driven features to advance your daily communication:&#xA;– Unlimited Accounts: Sign in and switch between an unlimited number of accounts on a single device.&#xA;– Nicegram Wallet: Your personal multi-chain, non-custodial Web3 wallet, now supporting TON and EVM, simplifies managing digital assets with comprehensive security features. Effortlessly send and receive tokens to and from your contacts in-chat, process crypto transactions with ease, and navigate through a broad spectrum of decentralized apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;App Lock - Lock &amp; Unlock Apps&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/app-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:21:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/app-lock/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction App Lock is a powerful and secure free application to lock Gmail, Google, Chrome, YouTube, Facebook and more. 1). Intruder Feature: When this feature is enabled, if the protected app is still unlocked, the protected app is unlocked more than 3 times. App Lock will enable the front camera to take a picture and save it. Lets you know who is trying to access your protected apps. 2). Camouflage Function: There are two camouflage functions to camouflage the app icon and camouflage the unlock page to make the app lock more secure and the protected app more natural.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of Choice of Love: Dating &amp; Chat App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/choice-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:37:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/choice-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction ”Choice of Love: Dating &amp;amp; Chat” is a highly popular dating and social networking application that provides users with a platform where they can seek new friends, establish long-term relationships, or simply find casual dates. It offers features such as profile setup, browsing and matching with other users, instant messaging, searching for nearby individuals, and more.&#xA;Affected version 4.11.3-gms&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of Phone Cleaner: Boost &amp; Clean Android App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/phone-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:37:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/phone-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Phone Cleaner: Boost &amp;amp; Clean is an app helping to analyze all the junk files, gather all useless notifications in one place and block them, sort large files into media files, audios, pictures and applications, etc.&#xA;Affected version 2.2.0&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.&#xA;The cryptographic parameter in fingerprint authentication is not configured securely and correctly, resulting in fingerprint authentication that can be bypassed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
