<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on zzz</title>
    <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on zzz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:26:31 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;SMS text messaging app&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/sms-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:26:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/sms-text/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Simple and fast SMS application that you can use to send SMS to your friends, family and people you know.Features:Night mode option, Color customization option, Block unwanted spam SMS, Organize all your messages in folders, Support for emoticons, Appointment for sending messages, Group messages, Delayed sending, Support dual SIM cards, Message search option, Customize fonts, Change text size, Fixed messages, Backup and restore all your messages.&#xA;Affected version 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;Nicegram&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/nicegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:25:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/nicegram/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Nicegram is an alternative Telegram client, equipped with a set of innovative AI-driven features to advance your daily communication:&#xA;– Unlimited Accounts: Sign in and switch between an unlimited number of accounts on a single device.&#xA;– Nicegram Wallet: Your personal multi-chain, non-custodial Web3 wallet, now supporting TON and EVM, simplifies managing digital assets with comprehensive security features. Effortlessly send and receive tokens to and from your contacts in-chat, process crypto transactions with ease, and navigate through a broad spectrum of decentralized apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of &#34;App Lock - Lock &amp; Unlock Apps&#34; App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/app-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:21:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/app-lock/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction App Lock is a powerful and secure free application to lock Gmail, Google, Chrome, YouTube, Facebook and more. 1). Intruder Feature: When this feature is enabled, if the protected app is still unlocked, the protected app is unlocked more than 3 times. App Lock will enable the front camera to take a picture and save it. Lets you know who is trying to access your protected apps. 2). Camouflage Function: There are two camouflage functions to camouflage the app icon and camouflage the unlock page to make the app lock more secure and the protected app more natural.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of Choice of Love: Dating &amp; Chat App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/choice-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:37:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/choice-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction ”Choice of Love: Dating &amp;amp; Chat” is a highly popular dating and social networking application that provides users with a platform where they can seek new friends, establish long-term relationships, or simply find casual dates. It offers features such as profile setup, browsing and matching with other users, instant messaging, searching for nearby individuals, and more.&#xA;Affected version 4.11.3-gms&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorrect Access Control in the Fingerprint Authentication Mechanism of Phone Cleaner: Boost &amp; Clean Android App</title>
      <link>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/phone-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:37:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zzzxiin.github.io/post/phone-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>Product introduction Phone Cleaner: Boost &amp;amp; Clean is an app helping to analyze all the junk files, gather all useless notifications in one place and block them, sort large files into media files, audios, pictures and applications, etc.&#xA;Affected version 2.2.0&#xA;Vulnerability description The following vulnerabilities exist in the implementation of the fingerprint authentication function of this app.&#xA;The cryptographic parameter in fingerprint authentication is not configured securely and correctly, resulting in fingerprint authentication that can be bypassed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
